

NAJMA ROBBIAZTI

08561821950 | najmarabbiazti@gmail.com

Cikini - Jakarta Pusat

A fresh graduate at Sekolah Tinggi Ilmu Ekonomi Y.A.I majoring in Management. Interest in administrator and digital marketing. Experienced in leading and managing a community with excellent communication skills, analytical thinking, and strategic planning to solve problems. I like to learn new things and continually seek opportunities to develop myself. Can work in a team or individually, with attention to detail with good critical thinking.

Work Experiences

DKI Jakarta Provincial Government - Central Jakarta, Indonesia

Aug 2021 - Nov 2021

Administrator

- Responsible for preparing the activities of the head of the bureau
- Responsible for receiving, recording, scanning, and inputting incoming and outgoing mail
- Responsible for recording incoming and outgoing bills
- Assist employees in verifying data into the My-Spak system
- Contribute to events held by the agency

PT. Surveyor Indonesia - South Jakarta, Indonesia

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

Marketing Corporate Internship

- · Contribute to a rating and awarding scheme project called I-SIM (Integrated Sustainability Indonesian Movement) for Cities
- · As a contac person for all cities in Indonesia
- Manage and create an attractive content strategy on Social Media I-SIM (Integrated Sustainability Indonesian Movement) for Cities
- Conduct reguler data collection on filling indicators on the platform I-SIM (Integrated Sustainability Indonesian Movement) for Cities
- · Responsible for data entry platform and verifying data for I-SIM (Integrated Sustainability Indonesian Movement) for Cities

Education Level

Sekolah Tinggi Ilmu Ekonomi Y.A.I - Central Jakarta, Indonesia

Aug 2018 - Dec 2022

Bachelor Degree in Management, 3.65/4.00

- Maintaining GPA to stay above 3.5 by actively asking and giving opinions in class.
- Participated in the National Competition in the Field of Financial Management Business Science (KBMK 2021).

Volunteering Experience

Relawan Covid-19 Nasional (RECON)

Feb 2022 - May 2022

Contact Tracer

- Provide education about prevention, transmission, and control of Covid-19 to the public.
- Detecting new cases of Covid-19, both from report data in SiLacak and from surveillance data in the community.
- Daily report and carry out close contact tracing of at least 15 close contacts for each patient in Pademangan.

Skills

- Soft Skills: Communication; Critical Thinking; Problem Solving; Leadership; Time Management; Detail Oriented; Team Work; Adaptable
- Hard Skills: Microsoft Office; Canva; Social Media